<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Atari 5200 SuperSystem, commonly known as the Atari 5200, is a second generation (1976–1992) video game console developed and distributed by Atari, Inc. It was released in November 1982 in North America at a retail price of $269. It was not released outside North America. The 5200's internal hardware was almost identical to Atari's 8-bit computers however it came with an innovative controller featuring a 360-degree non-centering joystick with a numeric keypad, start, pause, and reset buttons. The console was discontinued on May 21, 1984.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La Atari 5200 SuperSystem, comúnmente conocida como Atari 5200, es una videoconsola de segunda generación (1976-1992) desarrollada y distribuida por Atari, Inc. Salió a la venta en noviembre de 1982 en Norteamérica a un precio de venta al público de 269 dólares. No salió a la venta fuera de Norteamérica. El hardware interno de la 5200 era casi idéntico al de los ordenadores de 8 bits de Atari, pero incluía un innovador mando con un joystick no centrado de 360 grados, teclado numérico y botones de inicio, pausa y reinicio. La consola dejó de fabricarse el 21 de mayo de 1984.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
