<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Game Boy Advance (abbreviated as GBA) is a 32-bit handheld video game console developed, manufactured and marketed by Nintendo as the successor to the Game Boy Color. It was released in Japan on March 21, 2001, in North America on June 11, 2001, in Australia and Europe on June 22, 2001, and in mainland China on June 8, 2004 (iQue Player). Nintendo's competitors in the handheld market at the time were the Neo Geo Pocket Color, WonderSwan, GP32, Tapwave Zodiac, and the N-Gage. Despite the competitors' best efforts, Nintendo maintained a majority market share with the Game Boy Advance. As of June 30, 2010, the Game Boy Advance series has sold 81.51 million units worldwide. Its successor, the Nintendo DS, was released in November 2004 and is also compatible with Game Boy Advance software.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La Game Boy Advance (abreviada como GBA) es una videoconsola portátil de 32 bits desarrollada, fabricada y comercializada por Nintendo como sucesora de la Game Boy Color. Salió a la venta en Japón el 21 de marzo de 2001, en Norteamérica el 11 de junio de 2001, en Australia y Europa el 22 de junio de 2001, y en China continental el 8 de junio de 2004 (iQue Player). Los competidores de Nintendo en el mercado de las consolas portátiles eran Neo Geo Pocket Color, WonderSwan, GP32, Tapwave Zodiac y N-Gage. A pesar de los esfuerzos de los competidores, Nintendo mantuvo una cuota de mercado mayoritaria con la Game Boy Advance. A 30 de junio de 2010, la serie Game Boy Advance había vendido 81,51 millones de unidades en todo el mundo. Su sucesora, la Nintendo DS, salió a la venta en noviembre de 2004 y también es compatible con el software de Game Boy Advance.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
