<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Game Gear is an 8-bit fourth generation handheld game console released by Sega on October 6, 1990 in Japan, in April 1991 throughout North America and Europe, and during 1992 in Australia. The Game Gear primarily competed with Nintendo's Game Boy, the Atari Lynx, and NEC's TurboExpress. It shares much of its hardware with the Master System, and can play Master System games by the use of an adapter. Sega positioned the Game Gear, which had a full-color backlit screen with a landscape format, as a technologically superior handheld to the Game Boy.

Though the Game Gear was rushed to market, its unique game library and price point gave it an edge over the Atari Lynx and TurboExpress. However, due to its short battery life, lack of original games, and weak support from Sega, the Game Gear was unable to surpass the Game Boy, selling 10.62 million units by March 1996. The Game Gear was discontinued on April 30, 1997. It was re-released as a budget system by Majesco Entertainment in 2000, under license from Sega.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La Game Gear es una videoconsola portátil de 8 bits de cuarta generación lanzada por Sega el 6 de octubre de 1990 en Japón, en abril de 1991 en Norteamérica y Europa, y durante 1992 en Australia. La Game Gear compitió principalmente con la Game Boy de Nintendo, la Atari Lynx y la TurboExpress de NEC. Comparte gran parte de su hardware con la Master System, y puede reproducir juegos de ésta mediante el uso de un adaptador. Sega posicionó la Game Gear, que tenía una pantalla retroiluminada a todo color con formato apaisado, como una consola portátil tecnológicamente superior a la Game Boy.

Aunque la Game Gear salió al mercado con prisas, su exclusiva biblioteca de juegos y su precio la situaron por delante de la Atari Lynx y la TurboExpress. Sin embargo, debido a la corta duración de su batería, la falta de juegos originales y el escaso apoyo de Sega, la Game Gear no pudo superar a la Game Boy, vendiendo 10,62 millones de unidades en marzo de 1996. La Game Gear dejó de venderse el 30 de abril de 1997. En 2000, Majesco Entertainment volvió a comercializarla bajo licencia de Sega.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
