<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Commodore VIC-20 (known as the VC-20 in Germany and the VIC-1001 in Japan) is an 8-bit home computer that was sold by Commodore Business Machines. The VIC-20 was announced in 1980, roughly three years after Commodore's first personal computer, the PET. The VIC-20 was the first computer of any description to sell one million units. It was described as "one of the first anti-spectatorial, non-esoteric computers by design...no longer relegated to hobbyist/enthusiasts or those with money, the computer Commodore developed was the computer of the future.

The VIC-20 was called VC-20 in Germany because the pronunciation of VIC with a German accent sounds like the German expletives "fick" or "wichsen". The term VC was marketed as though it was an abbreviation of VolksComputer ("people's computer," similar to Volkswagen and Volksempfänger).</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>El Commodore VIC-20 (conocido como VC-20 en Alemania y VIC-1001 en Japón) es un ordenador doméstico de 8 bits comercializado por Commodore Business Machines. El VIC-20 fue anunciado en 1980, aproximadamente tres años después del primer ordenador personal de Commodore, el PET. El VIC-20 fue el primer ordenador de cualquier tipo en vender un millón de unidades. Fue descrito como "uno de los primeros ordenadores antiespectadores, no esotéricos por diseño... ya no relegado a los aficionados/entusiastas o a los que tienen dinero, el ordenador desarrollado por Commodore era el ordenador del futuro".

El VIC-20 se llamó VC-20 en Alemania porque la pronunciación de VIC con acento alemán suena como los improperios alemanes "fick" o "wichsen". El término VC se comercializó como si fuera una abreviatura de VolksComputer ("ordenador del pueblo", similar a Volkswagen y Volksempfänger).</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
