<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Sega NAOMI 2 is an arcade board developed by Sega and is a successor to Sega NAOMI hardware. It was originally released in 2000. Since it uses similar NAOMI architecture (but significantly beefed up), it is also fully backwards compatible with its predecessor.

The NAOMI 2 is significantly more powerful than the NAOMI, including a dual CPU setup, new T&amp;amp;L GPU, dual rasterizer GPU, increased memory, and faster bandwidth. This leads to games with much more polygons than a NAOMI game, rendered at much faster speeds, while the new T&amp;amp;L GPU adds advanced lighting and particle effects. It was also more affordable than the very expensive (and difficult to program) Sega Hikaru arcade system that preceded it. The NAOMI 2 was nevertheless more powerful than home systems at the time.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La Sega NAOMI 2 es una placa arcade desarrollada por Sega y sucesora del hardware Sega NAOMI. Salió a la venta en el año 2000. Dado que utiliza una arquitectura NAOMI similar (pero significativamente reforzada), también es totalmente compatible con su predecesor.

El NAOMI 2 es mucho más potente que el NAOMI, ya que incluye una configuración de doble CPU, una nueva GPU T&amp;amp;L, una GPU rasterizadora doble, más memoria y un ancho de banda más rápido. Esto permite crear juegos con muchos más polígonos que un NAOMI, renderizados a velocidades mucho mayores, mientras que la nueva GPU T&amp;amp;L añade efectos avanzados de iluminación y partículas. También era más asequible que el carísimo (y difícil de programar) sistema arcade Sega Hikaru que lo precedió. No obstante, el NAOMI 2 era más potente que los sistemas domésticos de la época.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
