<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Sega Genesis, known as the Mega Drive in most regions outside North America, is a 16-bit home video game console which was developed and sold by Sega Enterprises, Ltd. The Genesis was Sega's third console and the successor to the Master System. Sega first released the console as the Mega Drive in Japan in 1988, followed by a North American debut under the Genesis moniker in 1989. In 1990, the console was distributed as the Mega Drive by Virgin Mastertronic in Europe, by Ozisoft in Australasia, and by Tec Toy in Brazil. In South Korea, the systems were distributed by Samsung and were known as the Super Gam*Boy, and later the Super Aladdin Boy. The main microprocessor of the Genesis is a 16/32-bit Motorola 68000 CPU clocked at 7.6 MHz. The console also includes a Zilog Z80 sub-processor, which was mainly used to control the sound hardware and also provides backwards compatibility with the Master System.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La Sega Genesis, conocida como Mega Drive en la mayoría de las regiones fuera de Norteamérica, es una videoconsola doméstica de 16 bits desarrollada y comercializada por Sega Enterprises, Ltd. (SCE). La Genesis fue la tercera consola de Sega y la sucesora de la Master System. Sega lanzó por primera vez la consola como Mega Drive en Japón en 1988, y en 1989 debutó en Norteamérica con el nombre de Genesis. En 1990, la consola fue distribuida como Mega Drive por Virgin Mastertronic en Europa, por Ozisoft en Australasia y por Tec Toy en Brasil. En Corea del Sur, los sistemas fueron distribuidos por Samsung y se conocieron como Super Gam*Boy y, más tarde, Super Aladdin Boy. El microprocesador principal de la Genesis es una CPU Motorola 68000 de 16/32 bits a 7,6 MHz. La consola también incluye un subprocesador Zilog Z80, que se utilizaba principalmente para controlar el hardware de sonido y también proporciona compatibilidad con la Master System.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
