<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The FM Towns (Japanese: エフエムタウンズ, Hepburn: Efu Emu Taunzu) is a Japanese personal computer built by Fujitsu from February 1989 to the summer of 1997. It started as a proprietary PC variant intended for multimedia applications and PC games, but later became more compatible with IBM PC compatibles. In 1993, the FM Towns Marty was released, a game console compatible with existing FM Towns games.

The "FM" part of the name means "Fujitsu Micro" like their earlier products, while the "Towns" part is derived from the code name the system was assigned while in development, "Townes". This refers to Charles Townes, one of the winners of the 1964 Nobel Prize in Physics, following a custom of Fujitsu at the time to code name PC products after Nobel Prize winners. The e in "Townes" was dropped when the system went into production to make it clearer that the term was to be pronounced like the word "towns" rather than the potential "tow-nes".</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>El FM Towns (japonés: エフエムタウンズ, Hepburn: Efu Emu Taunzu) es un ordenador personal japonés fabricado por Fujitsu desde febrero de 1989 hasta el verano de 1997. Comenzó como una variante de PC propietario destinado a aplicaciones multimedia y juegos de PC, pero más tarde se hizo más compatible con los compatibles IBM PC. En 1993, se lanzó la FM Towns Marty, una videoconsola compatible con los juegos FM Towns existentes.

La parte "FM" del nombre significa "Fujitsu Micro", como sus productos anteriores, mientras que la parte "Towns" se deriva del nombre en clave que se asignó al sistema mientras estaba en desarrollo, "Townes". Esto hace referencia a Charles Townes, uno de los ganadores del Premio Nobel de Física de 1964, siguiendo la costumbre de Fujitsu en aquella época de asignar a los productos de PC nombres de ganadores del Premio Nobel. La e de "Townes" se suprimió cuando el sistema entró en producción para que quedara más claro que el término debía pronunciarse como la palabra "towns" en lugar del potencial "tow-nes".</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
