<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>FinalBurn Neo is a Multiple Arcade Emulator most popular for emulating Neo-Geo, Capcom, Konami, and Cave games. It is developed by the FinalBurn team and originated from FinalBurn by Dave and old MAME versions.

FinalBurn Neo is an active fork of the FinalBurn Alpha emulator, created by many of the former FBA developers.

The reason for the separation of the older branch, FB Alpha, and new spin-off branch, FB Neo, was due to an apparent disagreement between one Barry Harris and the rest of the main FBA team members over a licensing issue.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>FinalBurn Neo es un Emulador Arcade Múltiple más popular para emular juegos de Neo-Geo, Capcom, Konami y Cave. Está desarrollado por el equipo de FinalBurn y se originó a partir de FinalBurn de Dave y antiguas versiones de MAME.

FinalBurn Neo es un fork activo del emulador FinalBurn Alpha, creado por muchos de los antiguos desarrolladores de FBA.

La razón de la separación de la antigua rama, FB Alpha, y la nueva rama derivada, FB Neo, se debió a un aparente desacuerdo entre un tal Barry Harris y el resto de los principales miembros del equipo FBA sobre un asunto de licencias.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
