<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The PlayStation Portable (PSP) is a handheld game console developed and marketed by Sony Computer Entertainment. It was first released in Japan on December 12, 2004, in North America on March 24, 2005, and in PAL regions on September 1, 2005, and is the first handheld installment in the PlayStation line of consoles. As a seventh generation console it competed with the Nintendo DS.

Development of the PSP was announced during E3 2003, and the console was unveiled at a Sony press conference on May 11, 2004. The system was the most powerful portable console when it was introduced, and was the first real competitor of Nintendo's handheld consoles after many challengers, such as Nokia's N-Gage, had failed. The PSP's advanced graphics capabilities made it a popular mobile entertainment device, which could connect to the PlayStation 2 and PlayStation 3 consoles, any computer with USB interface, other PSP systems, and the Internet. The PSP also had a vast array of multimedia features such as video playback, and so has been considered a portable media player as well. The PSP is the only handheld console to use an optical disc format – Universal Media Disc (UMD) – as its primary storage medium; both games and movies have been released on the format.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La PlayStation Portable (PSP) es una consola portátil desarrollada y comercializada por Sony Computer Entertainment. Salió a la venta por primera vez en Japón el 12 de diciembre de 2004, en Norteamérica el 24 de marzo de 2005 y en las regiones PAL el 1 de septiembre de 2005, y es la primera entrega portátil de la línea de consolas PlayStation. Como consola de séptima generación, compitió con la Nintendo DS.

El desarrollo de la PSP se anunció durante el E3 2003, y la consola se presentó en una conferencia de prensa de Sony el 11 de mayo de 2004. En el momento de su presentación, la consola era la más potente de las consolas portátiles, y fue el primer competidor real de las consolas portátiles de Nintendo tras el fracaso de muchos aspirantes, como la N-Gage de Nokia. Las avanzadas capacidades gráficas de la PSP la convirtieron en un popular dispositivo de entretenimiento móvil, que podía conectarse a las consolas PlayStation 2 y PlayStation 3, a cualquier ordenador con interfaz USB, a otros sistemas PSP y a Internet. La PSP también disponía de una amplia gama de funciones multimedia, como la reproducción de vídeo, por lo que también se ha considerado un reproductor multimedia portátil. La PSP es la única consola portátil que utiliza un formato de disco óptico -Universal Media Disc (UMD)- como principal medio de almacenamiento; en este formato se han publicado tanto juegos como películas.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
