<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The CP System (CPシステム, shīpī shisutemu, CPS for short) is an arcade system board developed by Capcom that ran game software stored on removable daughterboards. More than two dozen arcade titles were released for CPS-1, before Capcom shifted game development over to its successor, the CP System II.

Among the 33 titles released for the original CP System included Street Fighter II: The World Warrior and its first two follow-ups, Street Fighter II: Champion Edition and Street Fighter II: Hyper Fighting.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>El CP System (CPシステム, shīpī shisutemu, CPS para abreviar) es una placa de sistema arcade desarrollada por Capcom que ejecutaba software de juego almacenado en placas hijas extraíbles. Más de dos docenas de títulos arcade fueron lanzados para la CPS-1, antes de que Capcom cambiara el desarrollo de juegos a su sucesora, la CP System II.

Entre los 33 títulos lanzados para el CP System original se encontraban Street Fighter II: The World Warrior y sus dos primeras secuelas, Street Fighter II: Champion Edition y Street Fighter II: Hyper Fighting.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
