<theme>
<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
<view name="system">
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>The Mattel Intellivision is a second generation (1976–1992) home video game console developed and distributed by Mattel Electronics. It was released in summer 1979 in North America at a retail price of $299. The console was later released in Europe (1981), South America (1982), and Japan (1982). The Intellivision was the first home console to use a tile based playfield and was the first game console to provide real-time human voices in the middle of gameplay, courtesy of the IntelliVoice module. The console was discontinued in early-1990.</text>
  </text>
  <text name="sysdescription" ifSubset="systemview:CoinOPS" extra="true" lang="ES">
    <pos>0.05 0.72</pos>
    <size>0.49 0.22</size>
    <fontPath>./../_inc/fonts/Exo2-RegularCondensed.otf</fontPath>
    <fontSize>0.024</fontSize>
    <color>EDEDED</color>
    <glowColor>000000C0</glowColor>
    <glowSize>2</glowSize>
    <lineSpacing>1.1</lineSpacing>
    <alignment>left</alignment>
    <verticalAlignment>top</verticalAlignment>
    <zIndex>50</zIndex>
    <text>La Mattel Intellivision es una videoconsola doméstica de segunda generación (1976-1992) desarrollada y distribuida por Mattel Electronics. Salió a la venta en el verano de 1979 en Norteamérica a un precio de 299 dólares. La consola se lanzó posteriormente en Europa (1981), Sudamérica (1982) y Japón (1982). La Intellivision fue la primera consola doméstica en utilizar un campo de juego basado en fichas y fue la primera consola de juegos en proporcionar voces humanas en tiempo real en medio del juego, cortesía del módulo IntelliVoice. La consola dejó de fabricarse a principios de 1990.</text>
  </text>
</view>
</theme>
